# **Giovani Velasquez**

Junior Full Stack Developer

I am a well-qualified self-taught Junior Full Stack Web Developer with more than two years developing real world projects from the front-end and back-end side. Proficient expectations in most used programming languages as HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP and MySQL to develop and/or integrate new features to run business operations. In order to speed up results, I use React library as my client side and Laravel Framework as my server side.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

**Digital Investments,** Guatemala, Guatemala City. Junior Full Stack Developer

08/2020 - 2021

- Collaborated with the team to identify and resolve software issues, gaining valuable experience in debugging techniques.
- Learned and applied new technologies and techniques, including Git version control and REST API development.
- Assisted in the development of PHP and MySQL web applications, gaining valuable experience in web development.
- Translated designs from Photoshop to HTML and CSS while ensuring that the UX and UI design are maintained

# Hivolts Electrical Inc, Brooklyn NY, United States

Licensed and insured electrical company

**Humar Resources Specialist** 

04/2021 - Present

- Specialist to recruit, screen, and interview job applicants and place newly hired workers in jobs.
- Handle compensation and benefits, training, and employee relations.

# **FREELACE PROJECTS**

### Real Estate Admin Application

 Real Estate admin application to track customers payments, building expenses and monthly report.

#### **CONTACT**

- 1290 Ocean Ave, Brooklyn, NY.
- +1 917-615-6927
- jsjosgiovani@gmail.com

#### **SKILLS**

## Front End Development:

- HTML5
- CSS3
- Sass
- JavaScript
- jQuery
- Tailwind

#### Back End Development:

- PHP
- MySQL
- RESTful APIs implementation

#### Web Services:

- REST/JSON
- Axios
- Web RESTful API consuming
- Postman

#### Key Skills:

- MVC Design Patterns
- OOP Paradigm
- Auth Token implementation

#### Version Control:

• Git/GitHub

# Frameworks:

- React
- Tailwind
- Laravel

# Languages:

- English
- Spanish

#### **EDUCATION**

Del Valle University Computer Science and Information Technology. 10/2013 - 06/2017

#### **OTHER**

 Udemy Certificate: Full Stack Web Developer with HTML5, CSS3, JS, AJAX PHP y MySQL.